{"Answer": "Changes in Diet and Lifestyle and Long-Term Weight Gain in Women and Men\n\nSpecific dietary and other lifestyle behaviors may affect the success of the straightforward-sounding strategy `` eat less and exercise more '' for preventing long-term weight gain .\n\nWe performed prospective investigations involving three separate cohorts that included 120,877 U.S. women and men who were free of chronic diseases and not obese at baseline , with follow-up periods from 1986 to 2006 , 1991 to 2003 , and 1986 to 2006 . The relationships between changes in lifestyle factors and weight change were evaluated at 4-year intervals , with multivariable adjustments made for age , baseline body-mass index for each period , and all lifestyle factors simultaneously . Cohort-specific and sex-specific results were similar and were pooled with the use of an inverse-variance -- weighted meta-analysis .\n\nWithin each 4-year period , participants gained an average of 3.35 lb ( 5th to 95th percentile , \u2212 4.1 to 12.4 ) . On the basis of increased daily servings of individual dietary components , 4-year weight change was most strongly associated with the intake of potato chips ( 1.69 lb ) , potatoes ( 1.28 lb ) , sugar-sweetened beverages ( 1.00 lb ) , unprocessed red meats ( 0.95 lb ) , and processed meats ( 0.93 lb ) and was inversely associated with the intake of vegetables ( \u2212 0.22 lb ) , whole grains ( \u2212 0.37 lb ) , fruits ( \u2212 0.49 lb ) , nuts ( \u2212 0.57 lb ) , and yogurt ( \u2212 0.82 lb ) ( P \u2264 0.005 for each comparison ) . Aggregate dietary changes were associated with substantial differences in weight change ( 3.93 lb across quintiles of dietary change ) . Other lifestyle factors were also independently associated with weight change ( P ( 0.001 ) , including physical activity ( \u2212 1.76 lb across quintiles ) ; alcohol use ( 0.41 lb per drink per day ) , smoking ( new quitters , 5.17 lb ; former smokers , 0.14 lb ) , sleep ( more weight gain with ( 6 or ) 8 hours of sleep ) , and television watching ( 0.31 lb per hour per day ) .\n\nSpecific dietary and lifestyle factors are independently associated with long-term weight gain , with a substantial aggregate effect and implications for strategies to prevent obesity . ( Funded by the National Institutes of Health and others . )\n\n", "Topic": "diet", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "level": 0, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"], "man": ["Participants"], "long term": ["Outcomes"], "120,877": ["Participants"], "u.s.": ["Participants"], "free of chronic disease": ["Participants"], "not obese": ["Participants"], "4-year": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "man": ["Sex"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"], "120,877": ["Sample-size"], "u.s.": ["Location"], "free of chronic disease": ["Condition"], "not obese": ["Condition"], "4-year": ["Duration"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": [], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Intensity": [], "Control": [], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": [], "Adverse-effects": [], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}, "Count": 1}, "Doggos_text": {"Sex": "The study was performed in women and men.", "Condition": "The participants were free of chronic diseases and not obese at the beginning of the study.", "Location": "The participants were from the United States of America.", "Sample-size": "There were 120,877 participants.", "Intervention-general": "The study assessed the impact of different dietary and life style factors.", "Duration": "The effects were evaluated at 4 year intervals.", "Outcomes-general": "The study measured long-term weight loss.", "Conclusion-general": "Specific dietary lifestyle factors are independently associated with long-term weight gain."}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296", "children": [{"Answer": "Losing weight is not always as simple as eating less and exercising more. It can be affected by diet and lifestyle choices. A recent study that took place over the course of twenty years has shown this. The study started out with a large sample size of participants who were free of chronic diseases and not obese and followed up with them every four years. On average, participants gained a little over 3 pounds in each four year time period. Weight increase correlated the most with eating potato chips, potatoes, sugary beverages, unprocessed red meat and processed meat. On the other hand, eating vegetables, whole grains, fruits, nuts and yogurt were all correlated with weight loss. Lifestyle factors also had an impact on the participants' weights. Physical activity was correlated with weight loss while alcohol use, smoking, not getting enough sleep and watching tv were all correlated with weight gain. ", "AssignmentId": "31LVTDXBL8V6QIG1U1VX55K4XGJRL2", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "APGX2WZ59OWDN", "Qualification": 0.7777777777777778, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "15-24", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes"], "free of chronic disease": ["Participants"], "not obese": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes-general"], "free of chronic disease": ["Condition"], "not obese": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "A", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_31LVTDXBL8V6QIG1U1VX55K4XGJRL2", "children": [{"Answer": "In a long term study of over 120 thousand Americans of both gender it was found that lifestyle choices have a strong impact on weight gain. Over a four year period an average person in the study gained 3.35 pounds. This gain was seen as connecting to an increase in the consumption of potato chips, other potato products, sugary drinks,red meat, and processed meats. At the same time diets were losing fruits, vegetables, whole grains, nuts, and yogurt. Other lifestyle choices like smoking and tv watching had weight ties as well. ", "AssignmentId": "33L7PJKHCHJORQ9A41RO0FZG1PM8TR", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A2O4QKZW68XFQA", "Qualification": 0.7777777777777778, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "long term": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "B"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_33L7PJKHCHJORQ9A41RO0FZG1PM8TR", "children": [{"Answer": "A study looked at how changes in multiple dietary and other lifestyle factors relate to long-term weight gain. It found that within 4 years, participants gained  an average of 3.35 lbs. Food associated with greatest weight gain were potato chips and sugary beverages. ", "AssignmentId": "37M28K1J0RY8WB6KP5XYU0I2UR9JAC", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A3D8ZG1VV5FO35", "Qualification": 0.7222222222222222, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "long term": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_37M28K1J0RY8WB6KP5XYU0I2UR9JAC", "children": [{"Answer": "A 4 year study on weight gain showed an average of 3.35 lb. increased servings of meat,  sugar sweet drinks and potato chips were blamed.", "AssignmentId": "3QBD8R3Z2247VXH0WHFCPTDO1HD4O7", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A1X8YRYS8MBDWX", "Qualification": 0.7222222222222222, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 3, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "60+", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "A"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3QBD8R3Z2247VXH0WHFCPTDO1HD4O7", "children": [{"Answer": "Lose weight by changing your lifestyle. Eat more veggies and less sweets.", "AssignmentId": "3MMN5BL1W0PYDYDKJNVGNKWDSVXM3C", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A2LTOS0AZ3B28A", "Qualification": 0.6666666666666666, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 4, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3MMN5BL1W0PYDYDKJNVGNKWDSVXM3C"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "While many have heard the advice \"eat less and exercise more\" when it comes to advice for losing weight, a research study has shown that long-term weight gain can be hard to control. Over 100,000 men and women in the United States free of obesity and chronic disease were investigated in terms of their eating habits and lifestyle changes over time. Over the four year period in which the investigation took place, participants gained around 3.35 pounds. This weight gain can be attributed to a higher intake of potato and potato products such as chips, sugar sweetened beverages, and both unprocessed and processed meat. A higher consumption of healthier foods such as vegetables, fruits, and whole grains could be attributed to weight loss. Lifestyle changes were investigated as well, and reduction in physical activity, smoking, alcohol use, sleeping habits, and watching television could all be attributed to weight gain as well as the participants dietary habits. ", "AssignmentId": "3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7A79GPKH", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A2ZQVXEOBZBOEF", "Qualification": 0.9444444444444444, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "15-24", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"], "man": ["Participants"], "long term": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "man": ["Sex"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7A79GPKH", "children": [{"Answer": "The article speaks about how diet and lifestyle changes can change your weight. Men and women that did not have chronic diseases and were not obese. They were evaluated in four year intervals. They found that weight change  was  associated with daily servings of certain foods.  Potato, sugary drinks and meats seemed to put weight in people. Better diet such as  eaters who included nits, vegetables and yogurt  did better with their weight. Lifestyle  factors  also came into play such as enouh exercise and enough sleep.", "AssignmentId": "3R2PKQ87NXTD31V34Q23RQY2AD0MIH", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A1X8YRYS8MBDWX", "Qualification": 0.7222222222222222, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 1, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "60+", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "woman": ["Participants"], "man": ["Participants"], "not obese": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "man": ["Sex"], "not obese": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3R2PKQ87NXTD31V34Q23RQY2AD0MIH", "children": [{"Answer": "A long-term weight prevention study with 120,877 healthy men and women confirmed a direct relationship between diet and lifestyle and weight control. 4-yr follow-ups show an avg weight gain of 3.35 lbs. Persons eating healthy and exercising lost weight whereas others gained.", "AssignmentId": "3YDTZAI2WY1MZ5AZQFH1DX0G80J41O", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "AGHKGWDYPVDFE", "Qualification": 0.6666666666666666, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "woman": ["Participants"], "man": ["Participants"], "long term": ["Outcomes"], "120,877": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "man": ["Sex"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"], "120,877": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["B", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3YDTZAI2WY1MZ5AZQFH1DX0G80J41O", "children": [{"Answer": "A long-term weight study of 120,877 men and women confirmed a healthy diet and lifestyle prevented weight gain. Otherwise, persons gained.", "AssignmentId": "3YDGXNSEO0F4A5UKP0QGS7NOMCA849", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "AGHKGWDYPVDFE", "Qualification": 0.6666666666666666, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "woman": ["Participants"], "man": ["Participants"], "long term": ["Outcomes"], "120,877": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "man": ["Sex"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"], "120,877": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3YDGXNSEO0F4A5UKP0QGS7NOMCA849", "children": [{"Answer": "Long term weight gain is affected by dietary and other lifestyle factors.", "AssignmentId": "3LRKMWOKB629RNGKUC75CCNU1LOZ24", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A37CE37LHUN8M6", "Qualification": 0.8888888888888888, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "60+", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "long term": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3LRKMWOKB629RNGKUC75CCNU1LOZ24"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "Dietary and other lifestyle behaviors may affect the success of \"eat less; exercise more\" weight management strategies.&#13;&#13;Investigations were performed in 3 groups of 120,000 U.S. non-obese men and women free of chronic diseases with follow-ups from 1986 to 2006, 1991 to 2003, and 1986 to 2006, evaluating changes in lifestyle factors and weight change at 4 year intervals. Adjustments were made for age, baseline BMI for each period, and all lifestyle factors. Results were similar among each group and sex.&#13;&#13;Participants gained an average of 3.35 lb over each 4 year period. Weight increase was most associated with increased consumption of potato chips, potatoes, sweetened drinks, unprocessed red meats, and processed meats. It was inversely associated with consumption of vegetables, whole grains, fruits, nuts,  and yogurt. Physical activity, alcohol use, smoking, sleep, and television use were also linked with weight change..", "AssignmentId": "3RYC5T2D74EWH3VZMTO4MMTO25FPRN", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A3CFULTNTVCYE2", "Qualification": 0.7777777777777778, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "woman": ["Participants"], "man": ["Participants"], "u.s.": ["Participants"], "free of chronic disease": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "man": ["Sex"], "u.s.": ["Location"], "free of chronic disease": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3RYC5T2D74EWH3VZMTO4MMTO25FPRN", "children": [{"Answer": "A large study looked at how a variety of specific foods and specific lifestyle factors affect long-term weight gain. More than 120,000 adults in the United States were checked every 4 years over 20 years. Among the findings: Those who regularly ate potato chips gained an average 1.69 pounds; those who regularly ate yogurt lost 0.82 pounds. Sleeping less than 6 or more than 8 hours a day led to more weight. Smokers who had newly quit gained more than 5 pounds. TV watchers gained about a third of a pound for each hour a day they regularly watch.", "AssignmentId": "36NEMU28XGYV4WF8T76ISH7AQXNMWW", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "AABCSDU3TZLNG", "Qualification": 0.7777777777777778, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "long term": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["B"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_36NEMU28XGYV4WF8T76ISH7AQXNMWW", "children": [{"Answer": "Long-term weight gain prevention means adjusting diet and lifestyle. Vegetables, whole grains, fruit, nuts, and yogart should be eaten.  Chips, potatoes, sugary drinks, red meat, and processed meats should be avoided.  Increased physical activity helps prevent obesity.", "AssignmentId": "3I3WADAZ9RPPRGL0AMYMULJ21BPO59", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A1E235KE3CSO7H", "Qualification": 0.7777777777777778, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "60+", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "long term": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3I3WADAZ9RPPRGL0AMYMULJ21BPO59", "children": [{"Answer": "Dietary and lifestyle factors independently attribute to long-term weight gain.  Factors include: carbohydrates intake, soda, and smoking.", "AssignmentId": "3AAJC4I4FHD9XJES1XDXBT9B3ILJZU", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A1E66M679AFI3S", "Qualification": 0.7222222222222222, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "long term": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3AAJC4I4FHD9XJES1XDXBT9B3ILJZU", "children": [{"Answer": "Diet and lifestyle behaviors are strongly correlated with weight gain.", "AssignmentId": "33CUSNVVNOX5T6HM13GT9J3TOCB88D", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A18V6K2TMWMSWD", "Qualification": 0.8888888888888888, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 4, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "60+", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_33CUSNVVNOX5T6HM13GT9J3TOCB88D"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "Long term weight gain was seen in men and women across the board wen a twenty year study was done. The study looked at 120,877 men and women who were not over weight nor had chronic health conditions at the beginning. Every 4 years individuals were evaluated and adjustments were made for age, baseline body mass index and lifestyle factors. &#13;&#13;An interesting component to the diet study was the increase of processed foods to the diets of the participants. This significantly increased weight gain for those people who weighed in every four years. Processed foods considered were potato chips, potatoes, soda pop and unprocessed red meats. an average of 3.5 pounds over the 4 year period were gained. Or one pound a year on average. If these individuals ate a significant amount of vegetables, whole grains, fruits, nuts and yogurt one could help alleviate that gain. The study also concluded that for people who smoked or were former smokers they also gained a bit weight. The study ended by saying if several of these factors were watched, obesity could be avoided. ", "AssignmentId": "3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7A7DNKPR", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A2LTOS0AZ3B28A", "Qualification": 0.6666666666666666, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "woman": ["Participants"], "man": ["Participants"], "long term": ["Outcomes"], "120,877": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "man": ["Sex"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"], "120,877": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7A7DNKPR", "children": [{"Answer": "Participants were studied over a four year period to study whether certain lifestyle behaviors had any effect on weight loss or weight gain. Researchers found that the behaviors more likely to gain weight included alcohol use, quitting smoking, watching television and eating foods such as potato chips, sugar sweetened beverages and unprocessed red meats. Behaviors leading to weight loss included physical activity and eating foods such as vegetables, whole grains, fruits and yogurt. ", "AssignmentId": "3LO69W1SU4YF1S7NEQ1L616XWA5GLZ", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A1Y22RY2G8RBAG", "Qualification": 0.8333333333333334, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "B"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3LO69W1SU4YF1S7NEQ1L616XWA5GLZ", "children": [{"Answer": "A recent study looked at the food consumed by people and weight loss.  Weight loss over time was reported in those whose diet contained fatty foods, red meat and carbohydrates.  Weight loss was less in people with diets containing vegetables, whole grains and fruits.", "AssignmentId": "3D4CH1LGEBEK0Q6EPTYV1SF2WLMG9A", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A1MRWMGHPEV8S6", "Qualification": 0.7777777777777778, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3D4CH1LGEBEK0Q6EPTYV1SF2WLMG9A", "children": [{"Answer": "The study confirms that eating fruits and vegetables, avoiding fatty and sugary food, and exercising leads to decreased obesity rates.", "AssignmentId": "3Q5ZZ9ZEVP0M6OYK359QXZT2M8P85Y", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A6CVN7CSC1K26", "Qualification": 0.7777777777777778, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3Q5ZZ9ZEVP0M6OYK359QXZT2M8P85Y", "children": [{"Answer": "Both dietary and lifestyle habits like inactivity can lead to obesity. ", "AssignmentId": "3QL2OFSM973S8GU3OHLHT2P73ZVNCO", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A2ZQVXEOBZBOEF", "Qualification": 0.9444444444444444, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 4, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "15-24", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3QL2OFSM973S8GU3OHLHT2P73ZVNCO"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "Lifestyle changes, including what a person eats, may prevent weight gain over a long period of time.&#13;&#13;Three separate investigations of 120,877 people took place between 1986 and 2006.  Each person wasn't obese and did not suffer from a chronic illness.  Changes in lifestyles and weight change occurred every four years.  Every four years the average weight gain was 3.35 pounds.  Increased weight gain occurred most frequently with the intake of starchy foods, sugar-sweetened foods, unprocessed red meat, and processed meat.  Decreased weight gain was observed most frequently with eating vegetables, while grains, fruits, nuts, and yogurt.  Participants who took part in physical activities lost weight.  Those who drank alcohol, smoked, slept more than 6 hours, or watched television also gained weight.&#13;&#13;The study as a whole proved that specific dietary and lifestyle factors do affect long-term weigh gain.", "AssignmentId": "34Z02EIMITY691479XE970TYIJ70TD", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A1E66M679AFI3S", "Qualification": 0.7222222222222222, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "long term": ["Outcomes"], "120,877": ["Participants"], "not obese": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"], "120,877": ["Sample-size"], "not obese": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "A", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_34Z02EIMITY691479XE970TYIJ70TD", "children": [{"Answer": "Most of the people have lot of weight. Because of their changes in diet lifestyle. In this task we talk about Changes in Diet and Lifestyle and long-Term weight gain in women and men. Now a days because of our lifestyle we cannot able to eat healthy food and need not able to maintain the diet. So it leads to weight gain. Most of women and men in US are suffered from heavy weight. To loss the weight we need to take healthy foods. We need to eat less and exercise more.", "AssignmentId": "3EKVH9QMEZP6OMBO2UI8LK4RE4BD2J", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A2T2WRW85CB935", "Qualification": 0.3333333333333333, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 1, "Education": "High School", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "woman": ["Participants"], "man": ["Participants"], "long term": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "man": ["Sex"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3EKVH9QMEZP6OMBO2UI8LK4RE4BD2J", "children": [{"Answer": "A recent study over the course of 20 years found that weight gain in people whose diet contained daily servings of potato chips, potatoes, sugar sweetened beverages, unprocessed red meats and processed meats was higher than those whose diets did not contain these foods.", "AssignmentId": "3P4MQ7TPPYX7X2D07RKDRNJV5PABBA", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A1MRWMGHPEV8S6", "Qualification": 0.7777777777777778, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3P4MQ7TPPYX7X2D07RKDRNJV5PABBA", "children": [{"Answer": "People who ate potato chips, potatoes, unprocessed red meats, sugared beverages gained more weight than people who didn't eat these.", "AssignmentId": "32KTQ2V7RE0KS0200WWQEXZZTOBM90", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A1MRWMGHPEV8S6", "Qualification": 0.7777777777777778, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_32KTQ2V7RE0KS0200WWQEXZZTOBM90", "children": [{"Answer": "To loss the weight people need to eat less food and exercise more.", "AssignmentId": "3X4MXAO0BH9M1CS0YF2ZEG1KXCXRWL", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A2T2WRW85CB935", "Qualification": 0.3333333333333333, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 4, "Education": "High School", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["C"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["C"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3X4MXAO0BH9M1CS0YF2ZEG1KXCXRWL"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "We performed prospective investigations involving 2 seperate cohorts that included 120,877 U.S. genders who were free of chronic diseases &amp; not obese @ baseline.  W/follow up times of 1986-2006, 1991-2003, 1986-2006. The relationships of changed lifestyle factors &amp; weight were evaluated @ 4 yr intervals w/multivariable adjustments mad for age, baseline body mass index for each period &amp; all lifestyle factors simultaneiously cohort &amp; sex specific results were similar.  Within each 4yr period they gained an average of 3.35 lbs on the basis of increased daily servings of individual dietary components.  4 yr change was most strongly associated with intake of potatoe chips, potatoes, sugar sweetened beverages, processed and unprocessed red meats &amp; inversely associated w/intake of vegetables, whole grains, fruits, nuts, and yogurt.  Aggregate dietary changes were associated w/substantial different physical activity, alcohol, tobacco use.  Former smokers, sleep(more weight gain with 6-8 hours of sleep) and television watching.", "AssignmentId": "3B837J3LDPHTUVBREASYHRYZPQJSR5", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "AU3EIPG4ZRRMZ", "Qualification": 0.7777777777777778, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some High School", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "120,877": ["Participants"], "u.s.": ["Participants"], "free of chronic disease": ["Participants"], "not obese": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "120,877": ["Sample-size"], "u.s.": ["Location"], "free of chronic disease": ["Condition"], "not obese": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3B837J3LDPHTUVBREASYHRYZPQJSR5", "children": [{"Answer": "my lifestyle and logn -term weight gain. each 4-year period, participants gained an average of 3.35 lb on the basis of incresed daily servings of individual dietary components, 4-year weight change was most strongly associted with the intake of potato chips, potatoes, sugar-sweetened beverages and yogurt aggregate dietary change were associated with substantial differences in weights change acroos quintiles. alcohol use smoking former smokers sleep.", "AssignmentId": "3TOK3KHVJU34EKZJYFDJS5XYTY4O77", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "ACB9BNW7MC207", "Qualification": 0.16666666666666666, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 1, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "4-year": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "4-year": ["Duration"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3TOK3KHVJU34EKZJYFDJS5XYTY4O77", "children": [{"Answer": "lifestyle and long-term weight gain in women . 6 months participants gained an average 6 kg and 4 years period, participants gained an average of 3.35 lb. weight gain with 8 hours of sleep. all lifestyle factor simultaneously.", "AssignmentId": "3R2UR8A0IB1YTZ5AGSHHM4AMVRKXOC", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "ACB9BNW7MC207", "Qualification": 0.16666666666666666, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 2, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "woman": ["Participants"], "man": ["Participants"], "long term": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "man": ["Sex"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["D", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "B"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["D"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["D"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["D"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3R2UR8A0IB1YTZ5AGSHHM4AMVRKXOC", "children": [{"Answer": "lifestyle and long-term weight gain in women and men. 4 year period, participants gained an average of 3.35 lb. ", "AssignmentId": "3CPLWGV3MPKQAIN0CXBQRCOZYEPN95", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "ACB9BNW7MC207", "Qualification": 0.16666666666666666, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 3, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "woman": ["Participants"], "man": ["Participants"], "long term": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "man": ["Sex"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "B"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3CPLWGV3MPKQAIN0CXBQRCOZYEPN95", "children": [{"Answer": "lifestyle long-term 4 year period, of 3.35 lb. ", "AssignmentId": "3X4MXAO0BH9M1CS0YF2ZEG1KXCZRWN", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "ACB9BNW7MC207", "Qualification": 0.16666666666666666, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 4, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "long term": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "B"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["C"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["C"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3X4MXAO0BH9M1CS0YF2ZEG1KXCZRWN"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "This text focuses on how changing diet and lifestyle impacts long term weight gain in both men and women.  It specifically discusses how  the \"eat less and exercise more\" mantra isn't a hard and fast rule, because it depends on a lot of other factors.&#13;&#13;The investigators monitored 3 groups totaling 120,877 American men and women (without chronic disease or obesity), and checked in on them in the following time periods:  1986 to 2006, 1991 to 2003, and 1986 to 2006.  There were evaluations at 4 year intervals with adjustments made for differences between participants.&#13;&#13;The study found that, within each 4 year period, the selected people in the study gained (on average) 3.35 pounds each time!  The biggest factors in weight gain: eating a lot of unhealthy food.  Other things that impacted weight gain: exercise, drinking, smoking, sleep and watching TV (unhealthy habits resulted in more weight gain).&#13;&#13;The overall message:  just eating less and exercising more aren't the only things that impact your overall health.", "AssignmentId": "3YOH7BII0ASNZJF0ILO6R2WST38KV0", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A5R0NQCWSPEJ9", "Qualification": 0.7777777777777778, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "woman": ["Participants"], "man": ["Participants"], "long term": ["Outcomes"], "120,877": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "man": ["Sex"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"], "120,877": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3YOH7BII0ASNZJF0ILO6R2WST38KV0", "children": [{"Answer": "A study that involved both men and woman in the U.S (approximately 120,877) came to the conclusion of the following: &#13;&#13;When people of either sex ate more red meat, sweetened foods, and specifically potato chips, then they would gain approx 3.35 pounds over a 4 year period. &#13;&#13;Where as people in the same group that ate more food like vegetables, whole grains, fruits, nuts, and yogurt, were not as likely to gain weight when they ate these foods. &#13;&#13;As well lifestyle choices such as smoking, drinking alcohol, and excercise affected weight gain/loss.", "AssignmentId": "3OLF68YTNAMSR9KO6F6DF2QA25LAF0", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "AW47H2ISJWAJC", "Qualification": 0.6666666666666666, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "woman": ["Participants"], "man": ["Participants"], "120,877": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "man": ["Sex"], "120,877": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["B", "A"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3OLF68YTNAMSR9KO6F6DF2QA25LAF0", "children": [{"Answer": "In this task we talk about Changes in Diet and Lifestyle and Gain weight in men and  women. Now a days people does not care about their health and weight. They eat unhealthy food and gain weight. To overcome this. We need to eat healthy food and Do exercise daily.", "AssignmentId": "3JNQLM5FT57PMYZGFBGW4XCWNDFL29", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A2T2WRW85CB935", "Qualification": 0.3333333333333333, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 2, "Education": "High School", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "woman": ["Participants"], "man": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "man": ["Sex"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3JNQLM5FT57PMYZGFBGW4XCWNDFL29", "children": [{"Answer": "An investigation on if Eat less, exercise more worked,  was performed on 120,877 people. They were measured at 4 year intervals. ", "AssignmentId": "3ATPCQ38J9VYR01JB5Y14NXQ8GCAYY", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A2LTOS0AZ3B28A", "Qualification": 0.6666666666666666, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 3, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"120,877": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"120,877": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["B", "A"], "Outcomes": ["C"], "Conclusion": ["C"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["C"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3ATPCQ38J9VYR01JB5Y14NXQ8GCAYY", "children": [{"Answer": "Increased weight gain is more directly related to ones diet than lifestyle.", "AssignmentId": "3LO69W1SU4YF1S7NEQ1L616XXWKGLN", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "AZZ5EFVB8UJRQ", "Qualification": 0.7777777777777778, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3LO69W1SU4YF1S7NEQ1L616XXWKGLN"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "The relationship between weight gain, lifestyle changes, caloric intake (amount of food eaten) and exercise is actually a lot more complicated that one might have previously thought. &#13;&#13;A study investigating more than 100,000 people over a period of 4 years in three different segments saw a correlation between aging and specific types of food eaten. On average, participants gained an average of 3.35 pounds. What appeared to have a substantial effect was the increased intake of chips, potatoes, added sugar, unprocessed and processed meat. All of these showed a marked increase in weight gain on average. Increased consumption of vegetable, whole grains, fruit, nuts, and yogurt actually had the opposite effect and showed an decrease in weight across those 4 years on average. &#13;&#13;Other lifestyle change such as alcohol use, smoking, sleep, and watching television also appeared to have an effect that varied across participants.", "AssignmentId": "3LUY3GC630LMZKBKDFQYH52O1V87PX", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "AZYUCL6B0YROY", "Qualification": 0.6666666666666666, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3LUY3GC630LMZKBKDFQYH52O1V87PX", "children": [{"Answer": "A study was performed among 120877 men and women in the US to determine whether specific dietary and lifestyle behaviors affect the success of the \"eat less and exercise more\" strategy for preventing long-term weight gain. The participants were free from chronic disease and not obese at the start and the  changes in lifestyle and weight changes were evaluated at 4-year intervals. Within each period, participants gained an average of 3.35 lb showing specific dietary and lifestyle factors are independently associated with long-term weight gain. ", "AssignmentId": "3NAPMVF0ZX0Q7DAEBHFMLSUVSTA72M", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A98E8M4QLI9RS", "Qualification": 0.8888888888888888, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 1, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "woman": ["Participants"], "man": ["Participants"], "long term": ["Outcomes"], "not obese": ["Participants"], "4-year": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "man": ["Sex"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"], "not obese": ["Condition"], "4-year": ["Duration"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3NAPMVF0ZX0Q7DAEBHFMLSUVSTA72M", "children": [{"Answer": "Does the adage Eat less, Exercise more work? A multi year study was performed on 120,877 individuals to find out. Every 4 years they were measured to see if they gained weight. Dietary and lifestyle factors showed this type of diet didn't work very well. ", "AssignmentId": "3X73LLYYQ2ZJPO5JA9ZI4TMNHRYNHW", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A2LTOS0AZ3B28A", "Qualification": 0.6666666666666666, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 2, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "120,877": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "120,877": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["C"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["C"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3X73LLYYQ2ZJPO5JA9ZI4TMNHRYNHW", "children": [{"Answer": "Lifestyle factors such as food choice, exercise, sedentary behavior, alcohol use and smoking are important factors in weight gain.", "AssignmentId": "3HFNH7HEMIZQSPN06V9HNN5R72CGQH", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A6CVN7CSC1K26", "Qualification": 0.7777777777777778, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3HFNH7HEMIZQSPN06V9HNN5R72CGQH", "children": [{"Answer": "Studies were performed on lifestyles like Eat less and exercise more.", "AssignmentId": "3ZR9AIQJUCUMSGPHUWD1ZSH64T140G", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A2LTOS0AZ3B28A", "Qualification": 0.6666666666666666, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 4, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["C"], "Conclusion": ["C"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["C"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3ZR9AIQJUCUMSGPHUWD1ZSH64T140G"}]}]}]}]}]}